Guide to the Church League of America Collection of the Research Files of Counterattack, the Wackenhut Corporation, and Karl Baarslag TAM.148
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series I: Counterattack Research Files, 1928-1967
  - Subseries V: Individuals, 1931-1960
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Hirsch; Bentley; Heimlich; Blanding; Halperin; Weltfish; Harap; Schnur; Winchell; Robinson] (14-0-3389 to 14-0-3399), 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Jacobs, Albert C.; Graham, Shirley; Brown, Himan; Pettibone Smith, Louise; Conant, Dr. James B.; Pusey, Dr. Nathan Marsh; Niebuhr, Reinhold] (14-0-3400 to 14-0-3406), 1949-1953 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Bass, Basil N.; Straight, Beatrice; Goddard, Paulette; de Havilland, Olivia; Winters, Shelley; Douglas, Kirk; Boyer, Charles; Cater, Douglas; Newman, Al; Ascoli, Max; Shaw, Bruno] (14-0-3407 to 14-0-3428), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Kaufman, George S.; Lancaster, Burt; Roberts, Stephen (Steve); Cantor, Eddie; Lee, Luen On; Sine, Julia; Seymour, Anne; Voss, Reverend Dr. Carl Hermann; Schnabel, Stefan; Conant, Dr. James B.; Rogers, Fred; Liff, Samuel; McNeil, Allan; Dula, John] (14-0-3429 to 14-0-3447), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Horne; Mugford; Ruggles; Hull; Kitt; Tandy; Murray; Field; Levant; Brandt; Hess; Sandburg; Ferber; Lorre; Carroll; Lewis; Cronyn; Heflin; Kinsey; Gunther] (14-0-3448 to 14-0-3479), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Welles; Hopkins; Greenfell; Allen; Lord; Orr; Bundy; Hausner; Kilburn; Paris; Frontier; Wasserman; Mitchell; Brozen; O'Connor; Baruchin; Molfetta; Singer] (14-0-3480 to 14-0-3512), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Ward; Doran; Herman; Douglas; Watson; Wechsler] (14-0-3513 to 14-0-3516), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Mandel, William; Ellis, Dorothy; Cotton, Joseph; Rathbone, Basil; Randolph, John; Albert, Eddie; Gardner, Ava; Tice, Anelle (Amelle); Porter, Sylvia] (14-0-3517 to 14-0-3527), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Mason; Spock; Gershwin; Moon; Chaplin; Jowitt; Condon; Edwards; Bettis; Lee; Melby; Green; Cunningham; Nelson; Beck; Dee; Bernstein; Hovey; Borowsky] (14-0-3528 to 14-0-3548), 1950-1953 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Index; Stuart; Watson; Hutchins; Goodman; McGuire; Tone; Cagney; Morritt; Wynn; Arthur; Clark; Bacall; Bogart; Wexley; Johnson] (14-0-3549 to 14-0-3583), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Van Paasen; Ryan; McKay; Fey; Potter; Hyman; Menkin; Hasiwar; Cairns; Robinson; Alvarez; Reynolds; Peters; Bush] (14-0-3584 to 14-0-3604), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Polan; Bissell; Argonsky; Pauling; Fairbank; Gelhorn; Henreid; Levene] (14-0-3606 to 14-0-3613), 1951-1953 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Hand, Learned; Wriston, Henry M.; Benton, William; Bowles, Chester; Price, Paul; Bryson, Lyman; Sullavan, Margaret; Harris, Julie; Kiekhoff, Professor John S.; Fonda, Henry; Peale, Reverend Dr. Norman Vincent; Silver, Henry A.; Warde, Harlan; Seymour, Anne; Buchman, Frank] (14-0-3614 to 14-0-3628), 1953 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Pizer; McGee; Fast; Block; Nearing; Katz; Forer; Stara; Louis; Murrow] (14-0-3629 to 14-0-3641), 1952-1954 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [CBS and NBC Biographies] (14-0-3642 to 14-0-3681), 1952 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Poitier; Lindsay; Gallacher; Ellington; Maynor; Armstrong; Basie; Caldwell; Kamp; Dennis; Spier; Henle; Jergens; Haggott] (14-0-3682 to 14-0-3706), 1953-1954 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Miscellaneous Individuals [Bershen, Louis S.; Campbell, Alan; Brooks, Geraldine; DeVoto, Bernard; Allen, Frederick Lewis; Hutchins, Robert; Kinsey, Dr. Alfred C.; Chase, Stuart; Quinn, Anthony; Hartman, Paul; Stern, M.; Crouse, Russel; Evers, Herbert; Arlen, Richard; Moore, Victor; Stone, Victoria (a.k.a. Rebecca Victoria Singer)] (14-0-3707 to 14-0-3729), 1947-1953 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Browder, Earl (14-1), 1938-1954 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Gailmor, William S. (14-2), 1946, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Struik, Dirk (14-3), 1949, 1951 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Reich, Harry (14-4), undated (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Steuben, John (14-5), 1950 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Rubin, Jay (14-6), undated (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Schappes, Morris U. (14-7), 1941-1949 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Epstein, Julius Victor Stefan (14-8), 1946 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Jaffe, Philip (14-9), 1946-1950 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Shapiro, Nathan B. (14-10), 1946-1949 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Ickes, Harold L. (14-11), 1939 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Foster, William Z. (14-12), 1940-1951 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - Robeson, Paul (14-13), 1938-1951 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - Quill, Michael (14-14), 1941-1949 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Derounian, Avidis (a.k.a. George Pagnanelli, John Roy Carlson) (14-15), 1946-1947 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Marcantonio, Vito (14-16), 1939-1951 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Velson, Irving (a.k.a. Israel Shavelson, Irving Shavelson, Charles Wilson) (14-17), 1946 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Loman, Charles (14-18), 1946 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Stuart, Helen (14-19), 1946 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Rooney, George H. (14-20), 1946 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Marion, George (14-21), 1946 (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Collins, Charles A. (14-22), 1946 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - Eisler, Gerhard (14-23), 1946-1949 (Box 17, Folder 7-8)
    - Wallace, Henry A. (14-24), 1948-1950 (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Senator Claude Pepper (14-25), 1942-1950 (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Draper, Muriel (14-26), 1948-1952 (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Yergan, Max (14-27), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Rosenberg, Milton (14-28), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Wolchok, Samuel (14-29), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Kirschwey, Frieda (14-30), 1951 (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Smith, Jessica (14-31), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Terlin, Rose (14-32), 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Lewis, Alfred G. Baker (14-33), 1947-1948, 1955 (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - Schuman, Frederick L. (14-34), 1948-1952 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - Connelly, Philip M. (14-35), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Durkin, James H. (14-36), 1947-1951 (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Corwin, Norman (14-37), 1947-1950 (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Berney, Leon W. (14-38), 1947-1951 (Box 17, Folder 23)
    - Sherwood, Carlton Montgomery (14-39), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Roger, Sidney (14-40), 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Condon, Dr. Edward U. (14-41), 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Davis, Benjamin J. (14-42), 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Isaacson, Leo (American Labor Party, NY) (14-43), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Dewey, Thomas E. (Governor New York State) (14-44), 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Stassen, Harold E. (14-45), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Smith, Ferdinand C. (14-46), 1948-1950 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Crum, Bartley C. (14-47), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Lampell, Millard (14-48), 1948-1951 (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Robinson, Edward (Frenchy) (14-49), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Shumlin, Herman (14-49A), 1949 (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - March, Fredric, Mr. and Mrs. (14-50), 1947-1951 (Box 17, Folder 36-38)
    - Rautenstraugh, Walter (14-51), 1946 (Box 17, Folder 39)
    - Gropper, William (14-52), 1949[?] (Box 17, Folder 40)
    - Hughes, Langston (14-53), 1937-1952 (Box 17, Folder 41)
    - Buckmaster, Henrietta (14-54), 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - McManus, John Thomas (14-55), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Sergio, Lisa (14-56), 1946-1949 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Shipler, Reverend Guy Emery (14-57), 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Sifton, Paul (14-58), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Banks, Murray (14-59), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Cotton, Thomas L. (14-60), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - O'Dwyer, Paul (14-61), 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Gaeth, Arthur (14-62), 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Addes, George F. (14-63), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Oxnam, Bishop G. Bromley (14-64), 1948-1953 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Kelly, Gene (14-65), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Ward, Henry F. (14-66), 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Mills, Saul (14-67), 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Oakes, Grant (14-68), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Forge, Maurice (Michael) (14-69), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - McMahon, Douglas (14-70), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Richter, Irving (14-71), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Melcher, Frederic Gershon (14-72), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Caughlan, John (14-73), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Saposs, David Joseph (14-74), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - Marshall, George (14-75), 1946, 1949 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - McDonough, Bernard J. (14-76), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Pressman, Lee (14-77), 1948-1950 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Young, Sidney (14-78), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Lubow, Paul (14-79), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Altman, Jack (14-80), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Smith, William (14-81), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Allport, Gordon (14-82), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Clark, Glenn (14-83), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Faber, Gustav (14-84), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Bishop, L. Melvin (14-85), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 73)
    - Matthiessen, F.O. (14-86), 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 74)
    - Robinson, Earl (14-87), 1949 (Box 17, Folder 75)
    - Niemeyer, Oscar (14-88), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 76)
    - Obermeier, Michael J. (14-89), 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 77)
    - Kroll, Leon (14-90), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 78)
    - Ryan, John F. (14-91), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 79)
    - Davis, Leon J. (14-92), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 80)
    - Barnes, Harry Elmer (14-93), 1947 (Box 17, Folder 81)
    - Draper, Paul (14-94), 1949-1949 (Box 17, Folder 82)
    - Thomas, Norman and Senator Glen Taylor (14-95), 1948-1953 (Box 17, Folder 83)
    - Richardson, Dr. Henry B. (14-96), 1952 (Box 17, Folder 84)
    - Metz, Julius (14-97), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 85)
    - Miley, Paul E. (14-98), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 86)
    - Johnson, Manning (14-99), 1941 (Box 17, Folder 87)
    - Dennis, Eugene (14-100), 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 88)
    - Gates, John (14-101), 1949 (Box 17, Folder 89)
    - Stachel, Jacob (Jack) A. (14-102), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 90)
    - Williamson, John (14-103), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 91)
    - Winston, Henry (14-104), 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 92)
    - Dana, Henry Wadsworth Longfellow (14-105), 1947[?] (Box 17, Folder 93)
    - Bradley, Professor Lyman R. (14-106), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 94)
    - Beall, Jack (14-107), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 95)
    - Garfield, John (14-108), 1947-1950 (Box 17, Folder 96)
    - Rogge, O. John (14-109), 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 97)
    - Adamic, Louis (14-110), 1948-1949 (Box 17, Folder 98)
    - Berne, Lewis Alan (14-111), 1947-1949 (Box 17, Folder 99)
    - Black, Algernon D. (14-112), undated (Box 17, Folder 100)
    - Goldsmith, Leonard (Len) (14-113), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 101)
    - Simmons, Ernest J. (14-114), 1948-1950 (Box 17, Folder 102)
    - Gaer, Joseph (14-115), 1948 (Box 17, Folder 103)
    - Belfrage, Cedric (14-116), 1948-1953 (Box 17, Folder 104)
    - Elliot, Harrison S., Mr. and Mrs. (14-117), 1947-1948 (Box 17, Folder 105)
    - Smith, Hilda Washington (14-118), undated (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Riskin, Benjamin H. (14-119), 1948 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Strauss, Leon (14-120), 1948 (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Baldwin, Roger N. (14-121), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Stowe, Leland (14-122), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Sentner, William (14-123), undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Spofford, Reverend William (14-124), 1948 (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Foner Brothers- Philip S., Henry J., Jack, and Morris (Moe) (14-125), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - Ross, Paul (14-126), 1948 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Hiss, Alger (14-127), 1947-1952 (Box 18, Folder 10-11)
    - Schrank, Robert (14-128), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Shapley, Harlow (14-129), 1949-1952 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Nixon, Russell A. (14-130), 1949, 1953 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Emerson, Thomas I. (14-131), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Smith, Edwin Seymour (14-132), 1949-1951 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Urey, Dr. Harold C. (14-133), 1953 (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Gauss, Dean Christian (14-134), 1949[?] (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Mann, Dr. Thomas (14-135), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Brooks, Van Wyck (14-136), undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Rubinstein, Dr. Annette (14-137), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 21)
    - Boas, Dr. Ernst P. (14-138), 1944, 1947 (Box 18, Folder 22)
    - Davis, Michael M. (14-139), undated (Box 18, Folder 23)
    - Webster, Margaret (14-140), 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 24)
    - Parker, Dorothy (14-141), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Snow, Edgar (14-142), 1947-1949 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Gayn, Mark J. (Ginsburgh) (14-143), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 27)
    - Lustig, James (14-144), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 28)
    - Scherer, Marcel (14-145), 1947-1949 (Box 18, Folder 29)
    - Berenholz, Anne (14-146), 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 30)
    - Yanoff, Morris (14-147), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 31)
    - Hirschmann, Ira Archer (14-148), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 32)
    - Fosdick, Raymond B. (14-149), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 33)
    - Loeb, Philip (14-150), 1949-1952 (Box 18, Folder 34)
    - Linfield, Seymour (14-151), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Fast, Howard (14-152), 1947-1951 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - DuBois, William Edward Burghardt (14-153), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Bass, Mrs. Charlotta A. (14-154), 1948 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Lauterbach, Richard E. (14-155), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Downes, Olin (14-156), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Stewart, Donald Ogden (14-157), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Adler, Larry (14-158), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Sweets, William M. (14-159), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Lathrop, Reverend John Howland (14-160), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Roe, Wellington (14-161), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Steel, Johannes (Herbert Stahl) (14-162), 1946-1949 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Johson, Reverend Hewlett ("Red Dean of Canterbury") (14-163), 1943, 1948-1950 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - Field, Marshall (14-164), 1947-1949 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Bridges, Harry (Deportation Case) (14-165), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Benson, Elmer A. (14-166), 1948 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - Acheson, Dean (14-167), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Wise, Rabbi Stephen S. (14-168), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Christoffel, Harold R. (14-169), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Strong, Anna Louise (14-170), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Melish, Reverend William Howard (14-171), 1947-1950 (Box 18, Folder 55-56)
    - Crouch, Paul (14-172), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 57)
    - Connolly, Eugene P. (14-173), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 58)
    - Nelson, Steve (14-174), 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 59)
    - Clark, Tom C. (14-175), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 60)
    - Crosbie, Paul (14-176), 1945-1949 (Box 18, Folder 61)
    - Hellman, Lillian (14-177), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 62)
    - Brand, Millen (14-178), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 63)
    - Da Silva, Howard (14-179), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 64)
    - Remington, William W. (14-180), 1948-1953 (Box 18, Folder 65)
    - Commager, Henry Steele (14-181), 1948-1953 (Box 18, Folder 66)
    - Jandreau, Leo (14-182), 1947-1949 (Box 18, Folder 67)
    - Jaffee, Henry and (wife) Muir, Jean (14-183), 1936, 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 68)
    - Van Doren, Mark (14-184), 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 69)
    - Pomerantz, Abraham L. (14-185), 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 70)
    - Bridges, Harry (14-186), 1948-1953 (Box 18, Folder 71)
    - Brand, Oscar (14-187), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 72)
    - Brown, Cecil (14-188), 1942, 1947, 1951 (Box 18, Folder 73)
    - Davidson, Jo (14-189), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 74)
    - Davis, Dr. Herbert John (14-190), 1948 (Box 18, Folder 75)
    - Drake, Alfred (14-191), 1948-1953 (Box 18, Folder 76)
    - Dean, Vera Micheles (14-192), 1947-1949, 1960 (Box 18, Folder 77)
    - Einstein, Dr. Albert (14-193), 1948-1953 (Box 18, Folder 78)
    - Graham, Dr. Frank P. (14-194), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 79)
    - Grauer, Ben (14-195), 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 80)
    - Ferrer, Jose (14-196), 1948-1951 (Box 18, Folder 81)
    - Field, Frederick Vanderbilt [and Field, Anita Cohen Boyer] (14-197), 1949-1951 (Box 18, Folder 82)
    - Foye, Hope (14-198), 1951 (Box 18, Folder 83)
    - Freistadt, Hans (14-199), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 84)
    - Gannett, Betty (14-200), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 85)
    - Guinier, Ewart (14-201), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 86)
    - Holliday, Judy (14-202), 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 87)
    - Hagen, Uta (14-203), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 88)
    - Hammett, Dashiell (14-204), 1950-1951, 1955 (Box 18, Folder 89)
    - Houseman, John (14-205), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 90)
    - Hovde, Bryn J. (14-206), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 91)
    - Hunt, Marsha (14-207), 1950-1951 (Box 18, Folder 92)
    - Isaacs, Stanley M. (14-208), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 93)
    - Ives, Burl (14-209), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 94)
    - Jessup, Philip C. (14-210), 1949-1950 (Box 18, Folder 95)
    - Roosevelt, Mrs. Eleanor (14-211), 1947, 1949 (Box 18, Folder 96)
    - Johnson, Beatrice Siskind (14-212), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Jones, Reverend John Paul (14-213), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 98)
    - Kasenkina, Mrs. Oksana (14-214), 1948-1949 (Box 18, Folder 99)
    - Kahn, Albert E. (14-215), 1946-1948 (Box 18, Folder 100)
    - Kamp, Joseph P. (14-216), 1945-1954 (Box 18, Folder 101)
    - Kraber, Tony Gerrit and Wilhelmina Kraber (14-217), 1948-1951 (Box 18, Folder 102)
    - Kravchenko, Victor (14-218), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 103)
    - Kent, Rockwell (14-219), 1949 (Box 18, Folder 104)
    - Reuter, Madalynne (14-220), 1949-1951 (Box 18, Folder 105)
    - Michelson, Clarina (14-221), 1949-1951 (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Lamont, Corliss (14-222), 1941-1954 (Box 19, Folder 2-3)
    - Lancaster, Burt(on) Stephen (14-223), 1948-1950 (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Lattimore, Owen (14-224), 1944, 1949-1953 (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Lavery, Emmet (14-225), 1947-1951 (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Lee, Gypsy Rose (14-226), 1950 (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Lee, Madaleine (14-227), 1950 (Box 19, Folder 8)
    - Leslie, Kenneth (14-228), 1944-1946 (Box 19, Folder 9)
    - Lev, Ray (14-229), 1949-1951 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Lewis, Fulton, Jr. (14-230), 1949-1951 (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Sacher, Harry (14-231A), 1949-1953 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Santo, John (14-231), 1947-1949 (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Rosenberg, Julius and Ethel (14-232), 1952-1953 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Stone, I.F. (14-233), 1946-1955 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Thomas, J. Parnell (14-234), 1947-1948 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Warne, Colston E. (14-235), 1950 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Weinberg, Joseph W. (14-236), 1949 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Weltfish, Dr. Gene (14-237), 1948-1951[?] (Box 19, Folder 19-20)
    - Hubley, John (14-239), 1944-1956 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Subseries VI: Organizations, 1928-1967; 1940-1965
    This series contains files on issues and organizations that Counterattack was monitoring in the course of its activities. Included are clippings, pamphlets, publications and other collected materials, as well as related correspondence and internal communication. Reports and draft reports generated by Counterattack are also present.
    Counterattack monitored a range of organizations, including nonprofits, educational institutions, unions, religious organizations, and government entities. There are also files on public policy subjects and some individuals. A number of folders, labeled "Illinois," deal with unions and Communist influence in farm implement and heavy machinery manufacturing in Moline, Illinois; Rock Island, Illinois; and Davenport, Iowa.
    - Organizations, Miscellaneous [American Association for the UN, Emergency Committee of Atomic Scientists, American Academy of Dramatic Artists, United World Federalists, WOMAN, Grenville Clark, WCFM, Rand School of Social Science, American Association for a Democratic Germany] (15-0-1A), circa 1947-1953 (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Non-Communist Organizations, Miscellaneous [Foundation for Economic Education, National Consumers League, Writers' War Board, American Life Convention, NAACP, Honest Ballot Association, Federal Burea of Investigation, American Action, World Festivals for Friendship] (15-0, 1-55), 1940-1947 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Non-Communist Organizations, Miscellaneous [World Education Service Council, League for Industrial Democracy, Freedom House, Veterans for Better Government, Patriotic Citizenship Association, American Nationalism Committee, Friends of Frank Fay] (15-0, 1-55), 1940-1947 (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Non-Communist Organizations, Miscellaneous [Lisle Fellowship, People's Lobby, International Student Conference, Society for the Prevention of World War III, Motion Picture Alliance, Youth Committee Against War, Non-Sectarian Anti-Nazi League to Champion Human Rights] (15-0, 1-55), 1940-1947 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Non-Communist Organizations, Miscellaneous [Civil Rights Defense Committee, Workers Defense League, Keep America Out of War Congress, National Sharecroppers Week, American Association for a Democratic Germany, Friends of Democracy, Common Council for American Unity] (15-0, 1-55), 1940-1947 (Box 19, Folder 26)
    - Non-Communist Organizations, Miscellaneous [American Institute for Economic Research, Threefold, National Meeting of the Engineers and Scientists of America Union, Thomas Paine Foundation, American Relief to Korea, Foundation for Economic Education, United World Federalists] (15-0, 56-150), circa 1951-1956 (Box 19, Folder 27)
    - Non-Communist Organizations, Miscellaneous [National Arts Foundation, National Bureau of Economic Research, Minute Women of America,World Organization of Mothers of All Nations, Forgotten Generation, Saturday Review of Literature, West Side Committee on Civil Rights, American Loyalty Society, American Action Inc.](15-0, 56-150), 1948-1958 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Non-Communist Organizations, Miscellaneous [Emergency Committee of Atomic Scientists, WCFM, Save the Children Foundation, Association of Scientists for Atomic Education, Washington Square Neighborhood Forum, Greenwich Village Center, National Council on Freedom from Censorship] (15-0, 56-150), 1947-1948 (Box 19, Folder 29)
    - Non-Communist Organizations, Miscellaneous [American Society of Helping Hands, Italian-American Labor Council, National Education Commission, Council of American-Soviet Friendship, Joint Anti-Fascist Refugee Committee, International Anti-communist Entente, IWW, Tool Owners Union, Passing Caravan Forum] (15-0, 56-150), 1947-1948 (Box 19, Folder 30)
    - Non-Communist Organizations, Miscellaneous [People's League for World Order, American Lecture Bureau, Catholic Information Society, American Heritage Foundation, American Viewpoints Inc., Indian League of America, Conference for a United May Day Celebration, Greek War Relief Association, Marshall Filed III, Luggage Workers, AFL] (15-0, 56-150), 1947 (Box 19, Folder 31)
    - Non-Communist Organizations, Miscellaneous [ACLU, Associacion de Periodistas Americanos, News Background Reports, International Solidarity Committee to Aid Labor Socialist and Democratic Anti-Fascists, WPA, Louis Bromfield, Louis Fischer, Raymond Gram Swing, Committee of 100, United Negro College Fund, All American Minutemen] (15-0, 56-150), 1947-1948 (Box 19, Folder 32)
    - Non-Communist Organizations, Miscellaneous [Animist Party, Solomon Barkin, Student Federalists Inc., Save Capitalism Committee, Un-American Activities Committee] (15-0, 56-150), circa 1947 (Box 19, Folder 33)